American Association for Labor Legislation Records 5001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  February 1917. 1 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  February 1917. 2 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  March 1917. 1 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  March 1917. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  March 1917. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  April 1917.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  May 1917. 1 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  May 1917. 2 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  June 1917.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  July 1917.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  September 1917.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  October 1917.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  December 1917. 1 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  December 1917. 2 of 2.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  Undated 1917. 1 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  Undated 1917. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  Undated 1917. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  January-February 1918
- Health Insurance, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  March, July, September-December 1918
- Health Insurance, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  December 17, 1918.
- Health Insurance, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  Undated 1918.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  January-February 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  March 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  April-June 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  July 1919. 1 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  July 1919. 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  July 1919. 3 of 3.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  July-August 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  September 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  October-November 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  November-December 1919
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  Undated 1919. 1 of 5.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  Undated 1919. 2 of 5.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  Undated 1919. 3 of 5.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  Undated 1919. 4 of 5.
- Health Insurance, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  Undated 1919. 5 of 5.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 39)
  No date. File 16 (Continued from Box 50)
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 40)
  Undated. File 17.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 41)
  Undated. File 18.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 42)
  Undated. File 19.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 43)
  Undated. File 20.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 44)
  Undated. File 21.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 45)
  Undated. File 22.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 46)
  Undated. File 23.
- Health Insurance (Box 51, Folder 47)
  Undated. File 24.
- Health Insurance - Fragmentary Material (Box 51, Folder 48)
  File 1 of 3. No date.
- Health Insurance - Fragmentary Material. (Box 51, Folder 49)
  No date. File 2 of 3.
- Health Insurance - Fragmentary Material (Box 51, Folder 50)
  Undated. File 3 of 3.
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1909 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  1 of 3.
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1909 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  2 of 3
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1909 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  3 of 3
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1910-1911 (Box 51, Folder 54)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1912 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  1 of 2
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1912 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  2 of 2
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1913 (Box 51, Folder 57)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1913 (Box 51, Folder 58)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1914 (Box 51, Folder 59)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1914 (Box 51, Folder 60)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  1 of 2.
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  2 of 2.
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1916 (Box 51, Folder 63)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 64)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1917 (Box 51, Folder 65)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 66)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 67)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 68)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 69)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 70)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 71)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 72)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 73)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1923 (Box 51, Folder 74)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1924 (Box 51, Folder 75)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 76)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 77)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 78)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1926 (Box 51, Folder 79)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 80)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1927 (Box 51, Folder 81)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 82)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 83)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 84)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 85)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1930 (Box 51, Folder 86)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 87)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 88)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1932 (Box 51, Folder 89)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1933 (Box 51, Folder 90)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1935-1936 (Box 51, Folder 91)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 92)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 93)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1938-1939 (Box 51, Folder 94)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents, 1940-1942 (Box 51, Folder 95)
- Industrial Safety, Diseases, and Accidents (Box 51, Folder 96)
  Undated
- Ind. Safety D+A Fragments, 1936-1937 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Labor Law Admin., 1912-1918 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Labor Law Admin., 1920-1925 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Labor Law Admin., 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Labor Law Admin., 1931 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Labor Law Admin., 1932-1934 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Labor Law Admin., 1935 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Labor Law Admin., 1936-1937 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Admin., 1938 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Labor Law Admin., 1940 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Labor Law Admin. Undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Factory Inspection, Calif., 1940 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Factory Inspection, Illinois, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Factory Inspection, Illinois, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Factory Inspection, Illinois, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Factory Inspection, Mass., 1931 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Factory Inspection, Mass., 1929 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Factory Inspection, Mass., 1938 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Factory Inspection, N.J., 1928 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Factory Inspection, N.J., 1929 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- Factory Inspection, N.J., 1930 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Factory Inspection, N.Y., 1929 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Factory Inspection, N.Y., 1931 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- Factory Inspection, N.Y., 1933 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- Factory Inspection, Wisc., 1929 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Factory Inspection, Wisc., 1931 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1910-1918 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1919-1921 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 29)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 31)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1925 (Box 52, Folder 32)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1926-1927 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1928 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1929 (Box 52, Folder 35)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1930-1933 (Box 52, Folder 36)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1934-1936 (Box 52, Folder 37)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 38)
- Old Age Pensions and Insurance (Box 52, Folder 39)
- Unemployment, 1909-1910 (Box 52, Folder 40)
- Unemployment, 1914 (Box 52, Folder 41)
- Unemployment, 1914 (Box 52, Folder 42)
- Unemployment, 1914 (Box 52, Folder 43)
- Unemployment, 1914 (Box 52, Folder 44)
- Unemployment, 1914-1915 (Box 52, Folder 45)
- Unemployment, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 46)
- Unemployment, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 47)
- Unemployment, 1914-1915 (Box 52, Folder 48)
- Unemployment, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 49)
- Unemployment, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 50)
- Unemployment, 1916-1917 (Box 52, Folder 51)
- Unemployment, 1917 (Box 52, Folder 52)
- Unemployment, 1918-1919 (Box 52, Folder 53)
- Unemployment, 1919 (Box 52, Folder 54)
- Unemployment, 1920 (Box 52, Folder 55)
- Unemployment, 1921 (Box 52, Folder 56)
- Unemployment, 1921 (Box 52, Folder 57)
- Unemployment, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 58)
- Unemployment, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  Dec. 31
- Unemployment, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 60)
- Unemployment, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 61)
- Unemployment, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 62)
- Unemployment, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  January-May 1924
- Unemployment, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  June 1924
- Unemployment, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  Undated 1924. 1 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  Undated 1924. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Unemployment, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  Undated 1925
- Unemployment, 1927-1928 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Unemployment, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Unemployment, 1929 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  Undated 1929
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  March-May 1930
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  June-September 1930
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  October 1930. 1 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  October 1930. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  December 1930. 1 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  December 1930. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  Undated 1930
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  January 1931. 1 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  January 1931. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  February 1931.
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  March-May 1931
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  May 1931
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  June-October 1931
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  November-December 1931
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  Undated 1931
- Unemployment, 1931 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  January 1932. 1 of 2
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  January 1932. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  February 1932.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  March 1932
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  April-August 1932
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  September-October 1932
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 33)
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 34)
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  December 1932. 1 of 5.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  December 1932. 2 of 5.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  December 1932. 3 of 5.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  December 1932. 4 of 5.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  December 1932. 5 of 5
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  Undated 1932. 1 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  Undated 1932. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  January 1933.
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  February-March 1933
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  May 1933
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  June-September 1933
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  October-November 1933
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  November 1933
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  December 1933
- Unemployment, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  Undated 1933
- Unemployment, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  January-March 1934
- Unemployment, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  April-July 1934
- Unemployment, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  August-September 1934
- Unemployment, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  October-December 1934
- Unemployment, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  Undated 1934.
- Unemployment, 1935 (Box 53, Folder 55)
- Unemployment, 1936 (Box 53, Folder 56)
- Unemployment, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  January-February 1937. 1 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  January-February 1937. 2 of 2.
- Unemployment, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  February 1937
- Unemployment, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  March-April 1937
- Unemployment, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  May, October, and Undated 1937
- Unemployment, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 62)
- Unemployment, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 63)
- Unemployment, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 64)
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 65)
  Undated. File 1.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 66)
  Undated. File 2.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 67)
  Undated. File 3
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 68)
  Undated. File 4.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 69)
  Undated. File 5.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 70)
  Undated. File 6.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 71)
  Undated. File 7.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 72)
  Undated. File 8.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 73)
  Undated. File 9.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 74)
  Undated. File 10.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 75)
  Undated. File 11.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 76)
  Undated. File 12.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 77)
  Undated. File 13.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 78)
  Undated. File 14.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 79)
  Undated. File 15.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 80)
  Undated. File 16.
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 81)
- Unemployment (Box 53, Folder 82)
- Unemployment - Fragmentary Materials (Box 53, Folder 83)
  File 1. Undated.
- Unemployment - Fragmentary Materials. (Box 53, Folder 84)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1910-1912 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1913 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1914 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1914 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1915 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1918 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1919 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1920 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1921 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1922 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1923-1924 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1926-1927 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1930 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1931-1933 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1934-1935 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1937-1942 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, undated (1) (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions undated (2) (Box 54, Folder 25)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions ND (3) (Box 54, Folder 26)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, Fragments (Box 54, Folder 27)
- Workman's Compensation 1906-1909 (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Workman's Comp. 1911 June-August (Box 54, Folder 29)
- Wages, Hours and Conditions, 1911 (Box 54, Folder 30)
- Workman's Comp, 1912 (Box 54, Folder 31)
- Workman's Comp, 1913-1914 (Box 54, Folder 32)
- Workman's Comp, 1915 (Box 54, Folder 33)
- Workman's Comp., 1916 (Box 54, Folder 34)
- Workmen's Comp, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 35)
- Workmen's comp., 1917 (Box 54, Folder 36)
- Workmen's Comp, 1918 (Box 54, Folder 37)
- Workmen's Comp. 1920 (dated) (Box 54, Folder 38)
- Workmen's Comp. 1919 (Box 54, Folder 39)
- Workmen's Comp. 1920 nd (Box 54, Folder 40)
- Workmen's Comp. 1921 (Box 54, Folder 41)
- Workmen's Comp. 1922 dated (Box 54, Folder 42)
- WC, 1923 dated (Box 54, Folder 43)
- Workmen's Comp. 1923 nd (Box 54, Folder 44)
- Workmen's Comp. 1924 dated (Box 54, Folder 45)
- Workmen's Como. 1924 nd. (Box 54, Folder 46)
- Workmen's Comp. 1925 dated (Box 54, Folder 47)
- W Comp., 1925 (Box 54, Folder 48)
- WC 1926 (Box 54, Folder 49)
- Workmen's Comp. 1926 nd (Box 54, Folder 50)
- Workmen's Comp. 1927 nd (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Workmen's Comp. 1928 dated (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Workmen's Comp. 1928 nd (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Workmen's Comp., 1929 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Workmen's Comp., 1930 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Workmen's Comp. dated, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Workmen's Comp. nd, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Workmen's Comp. dated Feb.-May, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Workmen's Comp. dated July-Dec., 1932 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Workmen's Comp. undated, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Workmen's Comp. undated, 1932 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Workmen's Comp., 1933 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Workmen's Comp. dated, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- Workmen's Comp. nd, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Workmen's Comp., 1935 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Workmen's Comp., 1936 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Workmen's Comp., 1936 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Workmen's Comp., 1937 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Workmen's Comp., 1938 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Workmen's Comp., 1939 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Workmen's Comp., 1940-1941 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Workmen's Comp., 1942 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Workmen's Comp. nd (1) (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Workmen's Comp. nd (2) (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Workmen's Comp. Fragments (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous, 1924-1930 (Box 55, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous, 1932-1940 (Box 55, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Research Materials undated (1) (Box 55, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous Research Materials undated (2) (Box 55, Folder 29)
- Unionism, 1906-1919 (Box 55, Folder 30)
- Unionism, 1920-1924 (Box 55, Folder 31)
- Unionism nd, 1924 (Box 55, Folder 32)
- Unionism, 1925-1926 (Box 55, Folder 33)
- Unionism, 1928-1930 (Box 55, Folder 34)
- Unionism, 1937-1940 (Box 55, Folder 35)
- Unionism nd (1) (Box 55, Folder 36)
- Unionism nd (2) (Box 55, Folder 37)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1910-1911 (Box 55, Folder 38)
- AALL Pamphlets 1915 (Box 55, Folder 39)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1916 (Box 55, Folder 40)
- AALL Pamphlets 1917 (Box 55, Folder 41)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1918-1920 (Box 55, Folder 42)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1921-1922 (Box 55, Folder 43)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1923-1925 (Box 55, Folder 44)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1926-1927 (Box 55, Folder 45)
- AALL Pamphlets 1928-1929 (Box 55, Folder 46)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1929 (Box 55, Folder 47)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1930-1931 (Box 55, Folder 48)
- AALL Pamphlets, 1932-1942 (Box 55, Folder 49)
- Broadsides AALL, 1909-1915 (Box 55, Folder 50)
- Broadsides AALL, 1916-1918 (Box 55, Folder 51)
- AALL Broadsides 1919-1922 (Box 55, Folder 52)
- AALL Broadsides, 1923-1927 (Box 55, Folder 53)
- Broadsides AALL, 1928-1940 (Box 55, Folder 54)
- Broadsides AALL undated (Box 55, Folder 55)
- Correspondence, 1910 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1911 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1912 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1913 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1914 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  Jan. - March, 1916
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  Apr. - Aug.
- Correspondence, 1916 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  Sept. - Dec., 1916
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  Jan. 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  Feb. - Apr. 1917
- Correspondence, 1917 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  May. - Sept.
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  Dec. 1918
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  Jan. - Feb.
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  March. - June
- Correspondence, 1919 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  Oct. - Dec.
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1920 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  Nov. - Dec. 1920
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  Jan. - March
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  March. - July
- Correspondence, 1921 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  Sept. - Dec.
- Correspondence, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 22)
- Correspondence, 1922 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  May - Dec.
- Correspondence, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  May - Sept., 1923
- Correspondence, 1923 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  Jan. - Mar.,
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  April - May, 1924
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  July - Sept.
- Correspondence, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 30)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1925 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1926 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  Jan. - Dec.
- Correspondence, 1927 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1928 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1930 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  June - Dec.
- Correspondence, 1932 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1936-1940 (Box 57, Folder 14)
- Undated Press Releases of AALL (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Undated Press Releases of AALL (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Undated Press Releases of AALL (Box 57, Folder 16)